The Edge is a drama, tv movie film directed by Nicholas Kazan.
A three-part anthology suspense program in which men and
women face life's ultimate danger zone.
Each episode is introduced by a mysterious figure known as The Watcher (Barry Sattels), who arrives on the scene just as
strange things being to happen - pushing men and women in crisis over the edge and into bizarre, unexpected actions.
The Watcher / Anthology Host, played by Barry Sattels.
Sheriff Emil Abel (Indian Poker), played by Rutger Hauer.
The Kid (Professional Man), played by Christian Slater.
Kenny (Black Pudding), played by Brad Davis.
Hilda (Black Pudding), played by Kelly Lynch.
Dorite (Professional Man), played by Bridget Fonda.
Jagged Edge is a 1985 American neo-noir legal thriller film written by Joe Eszterhas, and
directed by Richard Marquand, the last of his films to be released during his lifetime.
The film stars Glenn Close, Jeff Bridges, Peter Coyote and Robert Loggia.
A lawyer reluctantly takes the case of a man accused of killing his
wife, but remains uncertain if he is guilty or not.
The film received positive reviews from critics and was a box office success.
Loggia was nominated for the Academy Award for Best
Supporting Actor for his performance.
The tone is emotional.